SINA OLFATI

Full Stack Developer

🔀 sinaolfati6@gmail.com 📞 +989941669736 😲 Kermanshah, Iran 🛗 26/01/2003

https://sina-olfati.github.io/sina-olfati-site in https://www.linkedin.com/in/sina-olfati-872950233

https://github.com/sina-olfati

Profile

I'm a 20 years old passionate developer (React.Js + Next.Js + Node.Js). I've invested my youth hours in deep learning to optimize myself to add the most value to your company; Doubt that? Just visit my site, ask my former employers... Or hire me and watch my career for 1 month.

Leave anything you worry about to me; improving your site creatively? Leading a team? Making your work environment more friendly? What are you waiting for?

| Skills | | | |
|-------------------|-------------------------------------|-------------|-----------|
| React.js | • • • • • | Next.js | • • • • • |
| Node.Js | • • • • • | MongoDB | • • • • • |
| TypeScript | • • • • | PWA | • • • • • |
| i18next | • • • • • | Redux | • • • • • |
| Redux-Thunk | \bullet \bullet \circ \circ | Recoil | • • • • • |
| Rest API | • • • • | SPA | • • • • • |
| Axios | • • • • | Material UI | • • • • • |
| Tailwind | • • • • | Bootstrap | • • • • • |
| Responsive Design | • • • • | Docker | • • • • • |
| Git/GitHub | • • • • | Scrum | • • • • • |
| JavaScript | • • • • | CSS | • • • • • |
| HTML | • • • • | | |

Experience

08/2022 – 11/2022 London, England(UK)

JavaScript Developer

VModel ☑

- Led the web development team, consisting of 4 members, for 3 weeks; Increased quality and speed by 50%
- Helped the members with coding when they were stuck; Increased speed and teamwork spirit by 40%-60%
- Made unique pages by building user-friendly, interactive and innovative user interfaces; 60% improvement in user experience

Contact: Shinor Spellz - WhatsApp number: +447377919954

05/2022 – 08/2022 Tehran, Iran

Front-end Developer (React.js) Intern

Clickhub (Noavaran Dadepardaz click)

- Learned and applied useful front-end skills; being able to build sites 200% more professionally
- Learned: Redux Redux-Thunk, TypeScript, PWA, Material UI, Formik, Docker, Scrum, PSD to HTML & CSS

Contact: Nima Bakhshi - WhatsApp & Telegram Number: +989363806000

Languages

EnglishPersian (Farsi)Kurdish"Perfect" grade diplomaNativeNative

Portfolio

Sina's Site 🗆

• Technologies: React.js, TypeScript, PWA (It is installable), Material Ui, SPA, Formik, i18next (made it multilingual), JavaScript, CSS, HTML

Sina's Shop ☑

• Technologies: React, Redux, Redux-Thunk, TypeScript, PWA, SPA, JavaScript, CSS, HTML

Resume Template Sample 2

• Technologies: Next.Js, TypeScript, Tailwind CSS, JavaScript, CSS, HTML

Education

08/2021 – present Bachelor's of Teaching Science
Tabriz, Iran Allameh Amini University ♂

2018 "Perfect" grade English language diploma Qasr-e Shirin, Iran Padideh Academy of Foreign Languages

2016 Honorary diploma in mathematics

Kangaroo International Olympiad ♂